IMRAN MEHRR

Cell: 0300 9822999, Email: mehrr@hotmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am enthusiastic, energetic, adaptable, conscientious, and self-motivated individual with experience of implementing personal support plans which focus on the individual's welfare, needs, wants and interests. Have ability to manage a challenging caseload, while staying focused on giving a high standard of care to every client. Constantly maintaining and demonstrating a positive attitude towards clients, their families, staff, visitors and others. Keen to find a challenging position within a caring organization where I will be able to continue to increase my work experience & develop my abilities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MANAGER FINANCE & ADMIN

MAY 2013 TO DATE

RENAISSANCE GROUP - LAHORE MOTORWAY CITY - Pakistan

Manager Admin & Finance at LAHORE MOTORWAY CITY at its SITE office Since 2016. Major responsibilities include Planning and coordinating administrative procedures and systems and devising ways to streamline processes, Recruiting and training personnel and allocate responsibilities and office space, Assessing staff performance and provide coaching and guidance to ensure maximum efficiency. Monitor costs and expenses to assist in budget preparation, Monitor inventory of office supplies and the purchasing of new material with attention to budgetary constraints, Coordinate internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of projects, Manage changes to the project scope, project schedule and project costs using appropriate verification techniques, Track project performance, specifically to analyze the successful completion of short and long-term goals.

SECURITY CONTROLLER STM LONDON – U.K

APRIL 2011 TO MAY 2013

Security Controller at STM LONDON UNITED KINGDOM at its corporate office of Romford Road, Stratford, London, E15 4LJ from 2011 to 2013. Major responsibilities include safety of public at public places and private building and railway stations. Supervising and managing a security team comprising of more than 1000 personnel of different races. Inspecting site and developing and implementing security policies and procedures. Assisting in conducting security audits and preparing security budget.

GROUP MANAGER FINANCE ZAITOON GROUP Lahore - Pakistan

MAY 2003 TO APRIL 2011

Group Finance Manager (from Assistant Finance Manager) at ZAITOON GROUP at its corporate office Since 2003. Major responsibilities include planning and raising of funds, investments of funds and taking financial decisions. Proven record of developing and implementing financial and operational controls that improves Profit of the Group Companies.

FINANCE OFFICER ECHO WEST INTERNATIONAL PVT. LTD.

NOV 2001 TO MAY 2003

Finance Officer at Echo West International Pvt. Limited at its corporate office in Lahore-Pakistan. It is a leading construction and engineering based company having its operations nationwide and international level. It founded in 1992 seeking very good repute in the market and having a very significant number of successfully completed projects inside Pakistan and outside.

EDUCATION

M.B.A BANKING & FINANCE (Finance) Punjab University, Lahore Session 2004-2006
M.B in BUSINESS ECONOMICS (Fin and Econ) Punjab University, Lahore Session 1999 - 2001

IT SKILLS

Advance Knowledge of MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Internet Surfing, Browsing and related info.

REFERENCES

Excellent references available upon request